Harrison Russell-Lucas

Bio

- Bright, young, energetic and hungry for work,
- Good insight of today's pop culture and current trends.

 Always willing to go the extra mile to perfect my work. Most of my life has been working trades and using my hands. In doing so it taught myself hard-work and teamwork goes a long way.

 I find myself intrigued by the marketing side more of design.

Education

"Graphic Design Technology" Diploma

"Vancouver Career College" Apr 2020 - Jan 2021

"Carpentry" Level 1
"KPU" Jul 2015 - Jan 2016

Experience

Head of Detail Department / Kirmac Collision and Autoglass Improved not only communication skills but a leadership role. Jan 2018 - Present

Salesman and auto part delivery / B&J Auto Parts
For a small auto part store. Built social and customer service skills.
Jul 2016 - Nov 2017

Concrete Former / Femo Construction In a small teams showing me hard work and dedication. Jun 2015 - Mar 2016

Contact

Coquitlam, B.C.

harryrusselllucasgmail.com

https://harryson15.github.io/Airy/

604-375-1332

Skills





Hobbies







